// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let que6 = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which package manager is bundled with Node.js by default?",
      answer: "npm",
      options: [
        "npm",
        "bower",
        "yarn",
        "grunt"
        
      ]
    },
      
   
      {
      numb: 2,
      question: "Which method is used in Node.js to include modules?",
      answer: "require()",
      options: [
        "require()",
        "include()",
        "import",
        "fetch()"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "In Node.js, which of the following is an in-built event emitter?",
      answer: "EventEmitter",
      options: [
        "EventEmitter",
        "Events",
        "EventLoop",
        "EventYield"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "How can you read command-line arguments in a Node.js application?",
      answer: "process.argv",
      options: [
        "argv",
        "process.args",
        "arguments",
        "process.argv"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of the following is a core module for handling paths?",
      answer: "path",
      options: [
        "url",
        "dir",
        "path",
        "location"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following allows Node.js to be scalable?",
      answer: "Event-driven architecture",
      options: [
        "Multithreading",
        "Event-driven architecture",
        "Larger memory allocation",
        "High CPU usage"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Node.js uses _ programming",
      answer: "asynchronous",
      options: [
        "asynchronous",
        "synchronous",
        "Both A and B",
        "None of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What does the fs module stand for?",
      answer: "File System",
      options: [
        "File Service",
        "File System",
        "File Store",
        "File Sharing"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the following template engines can be used with Node.js?",
      answer: "Handlebars",
      options: [
        "Jade",
        "Vash",
        "Handlebars",
        "All of the above"
      ]
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "What is the default scope in the Node.js application?",
      answer: "Local",
      options: [
        "Global",
        "Local",
        "Global Function",
        "Local to object"
      ]
    }
      
  ];